[Music]
Pull that my palm. So proud to display.
Got latex and silicone and ready to
slay. Smoother, chunky, white, brown or
clear. Some for the bathroom, some for
out here. Colors on the shelf, I can't
decide. Flexible, waterproof, I'm
bonafide. Think is a milkshake or runny
is paint. Pick the right so your job.
[Applause]
Everybody's got off on their mind.
[Music]
Don't worry, you're going to find
it out every single night.
in your toolbox. Got to use it to off.
[Applause]
[Music]
Walked in the store, asked for some
coffee. Guy at the counter just started.
It got me and it did too. I said with a
smirk, "Hope this one fits. I've got a
lot of work. White or clear? The choice
is yours. Squeeze that trigger.
Open those doors.
[Music]
[Applause]
Everybody's got the balls on their mind.
Got to get Don't worry, you're going to
find
screw out every single line.
Your toolbox got easy, right? Go to
[Music]
heat.